{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"countingx:1_10__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947569589873","data":{"timestamp":" 947569589873"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_084616"," gameId":" c57068e9-c615-47a4-bf3f-6ee5360319b6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" countingx"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" START"," userResponse":" "," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"countingx:1_10__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947569631563","data":{"timestamp":" 947569631562"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_084616"," gameId":" c57068e9-c615-47a4-bf3f-6ee5360319b6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" countingx"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947569631654","data":{"timestamp":" 947569631654"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_084616"," gameId":" c57068e9-c615-47a4-bf3f-6ee5360319b6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" countx_1_10"," taskName":" Count to 10"," problemName":" countingx"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" END"," userResponse":" "," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 2"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947569656580","data":{"timestamp":" 947569656580"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_084616"," gameId":" f183284d-1b4a-4cba-993b-d0c98848e1cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na Dinasou wangu tunawaangalia ndege angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIMI"," userResponse":" MIMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947569657488","data":{"timestamp":" 947569657488"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_084616"," gameId":" f183284d-1b4a-4cba-993b-d0c98848e1cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Mimi na Dinasou wangu tunawaangalia ndege angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947569657712","data":{"timestamp":" 947569657712"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_084616"," gameId":" f183284d-1b4a-4cba-993b-d0c98848e1cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na Dinasou wangu tunawaangalia ndege angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIMI"," userResponse":" MIMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.show.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947569680965","data":{"timestamp":" 947569680965"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_084616"," gameId":" 773c568c-8e8f-4307-bce0-23a055938cc3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.show.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_awali_mkuyu-awali-ndege"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" awali"," userResponse":" awali"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.show.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947569686980","data":{"timestamp":" 947569686980"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_084616"," gameId":" 773c568c-8e8f-4307-bce0-23a055938cc3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.show.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ambao_kindi-ambao-mzito"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ambao"," userResponse":" ambao"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.show.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947569687727","data":{"timestamp":" 947569687727"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_084616"," gameId":" 773c568c-8e8f-4307-bce0-23a055938cc3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.show.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_ambao_kindi-ambao-mzito"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947569707745","data":{"timestamp":" 947569707745"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_084616"," gameId":" 2fe94203-9695-4f9d-8d18-54466d2c5dea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_alama_ikiwa-alama-tamaa"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" alama"," userResponse":" tamaa"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947569713536","data":{"timestamp":" 947569713536"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_084616"," gameId":" 2fe94203-9695-4f9d-8d18-54466d2c5dea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_alama_ikiwa-alama-tamaa"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" alama"," userResponse":" alama"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947569720368","data":{"timestamp":" 947569720368"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_084616"," gameId":" 2fe94203-9695-4f9d-8d18-54466d2c5dea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kindi_kindi-pekee-hajui"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kindi"," userResponse":" hajui"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947569726321","data":{"timestamp":" 947569726321"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_084616"," gameId":" 2fe94203-9695-4f9d-8d18-54466d2c5dea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kindi_kindi-pekee-hajui"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kindi"," userResponse":" pekee"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947569732548","data":{"timestamp":" 947569732548"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_084616"," gameId":" 2fe94203-9695-4f9d-8d18-54466d2c5dea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kindi_kindi-pekee-hajui"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kindi"," userResponse":" kindi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947569741322","data":{"timestamp":" 947569741322"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_084616"," gameId":" 2fe94203-9695-4f9d-8d18-54466d2c5dea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_shina_macho-shina-apiyo"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" shina"," userResponse":" macho"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947569747132","data":{"timestamp":" 947569747132"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_084616"," gameId":" 2fe94203-9695-4f9d-8d18-54466d2c5dea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_shina_macho-shina-apiyo"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" shina"," userResponse":" apiyo"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947569753257","data":{"timestamp":" 947569753257"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_084616"," gameId":" 2fe94203-9695-4f9d-8d18-54466d2c5dea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_shina_macho-shina-apiyo"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" shina"," userResponse":" shina"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947569758430","data":{"timestamp":" 947569758430"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_084616"," gameId":" 2fe94203-9695-4f9d-8d18-54466d2c5dea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_nyuki_jogoo-nyuki-mpaka"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" nyuki"," userResponse":" nyuki"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947569764103","data":{"timestamp":" 947569764103"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_084616"," gameId":" 2fe94203-9695-4f9d-8d18-54466d2c5dea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kukaa_nyigu-kofia-kukaa"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kukaa"," userResponse":" kofia"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947569770253","data":{"timestamp":" 947569770253"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_084616"," gameId":" 2fe94203-9695-4f9d-8d18-54466d2c5dea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kukaa_nyigu-kofia-kukaa"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kukaa"," userResponse":" kukaa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947569776642","data":{"timestamp":" 947569776642"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_084616"," gameId":" 2fe94203-9695-4f9d-8d18-54466d2c5dea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_jamii_chake-jamii-erosi"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" jamii"," userResponse":" erosi"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947569789628","data":{"timestamp":" 947569789627"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_084616"," gameId":" 2fe94203-9695-4f9d-8d18-54466d2c5dea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_jamii_chake-jamii-erosi"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" jamii"," userResponse":" jamii"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947569796247","data":{"timestamp":" 947569796247"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_084616"," gameId":" 2fe94203-9695-4f9d-8d18-54466d2c5dea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_miguu_ofisi-mungu-miguu"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" miguu"," userResponse":" mungu"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947569801947","data":{"timestamp":" 947569801947"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_084616"," gameId":" 2fe94203-9695-4f9d-8d18-54466d2c5dea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_miguu_ofisi-mungu-miguu"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" miguu"," userResponse":" miguu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947569807229","data":{"timestamp":" 947569807228"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_084616"," gameId":" 2fe94203-9695-4f9d-8d18-54466d2c5dea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_asije_asije-mengi-wingi"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" asije"," userResponse":" wingi"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947569813398","data":{"timestamp":" 947569813398"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_084616"," gameId":" 2fe94203-9695-4f9d-8d18-54466d2c5dea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_asije_asije-mengi-wingi"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" asije"," userResponse":" mengi"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947569819361","data":{"timestamp":" 947569819361"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_084616"," gameId":" 2fe94203-9695-4f9d-8d18-54466d2c5dea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_asije_asije-mengi-wingi"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" asije"," userResponse":" asije"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947569824840","data":{"timestamp":" 947569824840"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_084616"," gameId":" 2fe94203-9695-4f9d-8d18-54466d2c5dea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kutoa_fimbo-kutoa-asali"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kutoa"," userResponse":" asali"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947569830582","data":{"timestamp":" 947569830582"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_084616"," gameId":" 2fe94203-9695-4f9d-8d18-54466d2c5dea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kutoa_fimbo-kutoa-asali"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kutoa"," userResponse":" kutoa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947569836776","data":{"timestamp":" 947569836775"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_084616"," gameId":" 2fe94203-9695-4f9d-8d18-54466d2c5dea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_tamaa_kizee-tamaa-vipya"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" tamaa"," userResponse":" kizee"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947569842408","data":{"timestamp":" 947569842407"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_084616"," gameId":" 2fe94203-9695-4f9d-8d18-54466d2c5dea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_tamaa_kizee-tamaa-vipya"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" tamaa"," userResponse":" vipya"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947569849454","data":{"timestamp":" 947569849454"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_084616"," gameId":" 2fe94203-9695-4f9d-8d18-54466d2c5dea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_tamaa_kizee-tamaa-vipya"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" tamaa"," userResponse":" tamaa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947569855249","data":{"timestamp":" 947569855245"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_084616"," gameId":" 2fe94203-9695-4f9d-8d18-54466d2c5dea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_tamaa_kizee-tamaa-vipya"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.show.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947569879625","data":{"timestamp":" 947569879625"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_084616"," gameId":" 17a325b1-48f7-42f3-819b-136bd11af547"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.show.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ndani_ndani-aliye-twiga"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ndani"," userResponse":" ndani"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.show.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947569885093","data":{"timestamp":" 947569885093"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_084616"," gameId":" 17a325b1-48f7-42f3-819b-136bd11af547"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.show.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mbuni_mbuni-ndizi-ukiwa"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mbuni"," userResponse":" mbuni"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.show.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947569891515","data":{"timestamp":" 947569891514"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_084616"," gameId":" 17a325b1-48f7-42f3-819b-136bd11af547"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.show.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_sauti_sauti-mwitu-arudi"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" sauti"," userResponse":" sauti"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.show.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947569899037","data":{"timestamp":" 947569899037"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_084616"," gameId":" 17a325b1-48f7-42f3-819b-136bd11af547"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.show.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_awali_mkuyu-awali-ndege"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" awali"," userResponse":" mkuyu"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.show.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947569905789","data":{"timestamp":" 947569905789"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_084616"," gameId":" 17a325b1-48f7-42f3-819b-136bd11af547"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.show.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_awali_mkuyu-awali-ndege"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" awali"," userResponse":" awali"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.show.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947569912393","data":{"timestamp":" 947569912393"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_084616"," gameId":" 17a325b1-48f7-42f3-819b-136bd11af547"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.show.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ofisi_vumbi-ofisi-mpaka"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ofisi"," userResponse":" ofisi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.show.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947569917596","data":{"timestamp":" 947569917595"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_084616"," gameId":" 17a325b1-48f7-42f3-819b-136bd11af547"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.show.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_nyigu_nyigu-ukiwa-mjoma"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" nyigu"," userResponse":" nyigu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.show.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947569922384","data":{"timestamp":" 947569922384"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_084616"," gameId":" 17a325b1-48f7-42f3-819b-136bd11af547"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.show.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mlima_mlima-mende-umati"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mlima"," userResponse":" mlima"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.show.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947569931260","data":{"timestamp":" 947569931260"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_084616"," gameId":" 17a325b1-48f7-42f3-819b-136bd11af547"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.show.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mende_treni-mende-mkoba"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mende"," userResponse":" mende"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.show.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947569938391","data":{"timestamp":" 947569938391"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_084616"," gameId":" 17a325b1-48f7-42f3-819b-136bd11af547"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.show.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mpira_sivyo-swala-mpira"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mpira"," userResponse":" swala"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.show.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947569944343","data":{"timestamp":" 947569944343"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_084616"," gameId":" 17a325b1-48f7-42f3-819b-136bd11af547"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.show.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mpira_sivyo-swala-mpira"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mpira"," userResponse":" mpira"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.show.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947569950495","data":{"timestamp":" 947569950495"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_084616"," gameId":" 17a325b1-48f7-42f3-819b-136bd11af547"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.show.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ambao_kindi-ambao-mzito"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ambao"," userResponse":" ambao"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.show.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947569956260","data":{"timestamp":" 947569956258"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_084616"," gameId":" 17a325b1-48f7-42f3-819b-136bd11af547"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.show.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_ambao_kindi-ambao-mzito"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947569980716","data":{"timestamp":" 947569980716"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_084616"," gameId":" 15cba5f4-ed70-40d5-a005-9e8c4f828573"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_miguu_ofisi-mungu-miguu"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" miguu"," userResponse":" mungu"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947569986302","data":{"timestamp":" 947569986302"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_084616"," gameId":" 15cba5f4-ed70-40d5-a005-9e8c4f828573"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_miguu_ofisi-mungu-miguu"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" miguu"," userResponse":" miguu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947569993534","data":{"timestamp":" 947569993533"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_084616"," gameId":" 15cba5f4-ed70-40d5-a005-9e8c4f828573"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_asije_asije-mengi-wingi"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" asije"," userResponse":" mengi"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947569999521","data":{"timestamp":" 947569999521"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_084616"," gameId":" 15cba5f4-ed70-40d5-a005-9e8c4f828573"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_asije_asije-mengi-wingi"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" asije"," userResponse":" wingi"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947570005925","data":{"timestamp":" 947570005925"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_084616"," gameId":" 15cba5f4-ed70-40d5-a005-9e8c4f828573"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_asije_asije-mengi-wingi"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" asije"," userResponse":" asije"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947570011480","data":{"timestamp":" 947570011479"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_084616"," gameId":" 15cba5f4-ed70-40d5-a005-9e8c4f828573"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_jamii_chake-jamii-erosi"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" jamii"," userResponse":" jamii"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947570016674","data":{"timestamp":" 947570016674"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_084616"," gameId":" 15cba5f4-ed70-40d5-a005-9e8c4f828573"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kindi_kindi-pekee-hajui"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kindi"," userResponse":" pekee"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947570022976","data":{"timestamp":" 947570022976"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_084616"," gameId":" 15cba5f4-ed70-40d5-a005-9e8c4f828573"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kindi_kindi-pekee-hajui"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kindi"," userResponse":" hajui"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947570029194","data":{"timestamp":" 947570029194"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_084616"," gameId":" 15cba5f4-ed70-40d5-a005-9e8c4f828573"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kindi_kindi-pekee-hajui"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kindi"," userResponse":" kindi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947570035397","data":{"timestamp":" 947570035397"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_084616"," gameId":" 15cba5f4-ed70-40d5-a005-9e8c4f828573"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_tamaa_kizee-tamaa-vipya"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" tamaa"," userResponse":" kizee"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947570041343","data":{"timestamp":" 947570041343"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_084616"," gameId":" 15cba5f4-ed70-40d5-a005-9e8c4f828573"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_tamaa_kizee-tamaa-vipya"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" tamaa"," userResponse":" tamaa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947570051470","data":{"timestamp":" 947570051470"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_084616"," gameId":" 15cba5f4-ed70-40d5-a005-9e8c4f828573"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_nyuki_jogoo-nyuki-mpaka"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" nyuki"," userResponse":" mpaka"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947570056988","data":{"timestamp":" 947570056988"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_084616"," gameId":" 15cba5f4-ed70-40d5-a005-9e8c4f828573"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_nyuki_jogoo-nyuki-mpaka"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" nyuki"," userResponse":" nyuki"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947570063548","data":{"timestamp":" 947570063547"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_084616"," gameId":" 15cba5f4-ed70-40d5-a005-9e8c4f828573"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kutoa_fimbo-kutoa-asali"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kutoa"," userResponse":" kutoa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947570069690","data":{"timestamp":" 947570069690"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_084616"," gameId":" 15cba5f4-ed70-40d5-a005-9e8c4f828573"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_shina_macho-shina-apiyo"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" shina"," userResponse":" shina"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947570075090","data":{"timestamp":" 947570075090"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_084616"," gameId":" 15cba5f4-ed70-40d5-a005-9e8c4f828573"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kukaa_nyigu-kofia-kukaa"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kukaa"," userResponse":" nyigu"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947570080924","data":{"timestamp":" 947570080924"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_084616"," gameId":" 15cba5f4-ed70-40d5-a005-9e8c4f828573"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kukaa_nyigu-kofia-kukaa"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kukaa"," userResponse":" kukaa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947570086538","data":{"timestamp":" 947570086538"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_084616"," gameId":" 15cba5f4-ed70-40d5-a005-9e8c4f828573"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_alama_ikiwa-alama-tamaa"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" alama"," userResponse":" tamaa"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947570092415","data":{"timestamp":" 947570092415"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_084616"," gameId":" 15cba5f4-ed70-40d5-a005-9e8c4f828573"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_alama_ikiwa-alama-tamaa"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" alama"," userResponse":" alama"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947570098209","data":{"timestamp":" 947570098207"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_084616"," gameId":" 15cba5f4-ed70-40d5-a005-9e8c4f828573"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_alama_ikiwa-alama-tamaa"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947570121028","data":{"timestamp":" 947570121028"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_084616"," gameId":" 5d8c8bf6-4776-4fa0-8704-5008d452a3ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kutoa_fimbo-kutoa-asali"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kutoa"," userResponse":" asali"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947570127214","data":{"timestamp":" 947570127214"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_084616"," gameId":" 5d8c8bf6-4776-4fa0-8704-5008d452a3ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kutoa_fimbo-kutoa-asali"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kutoa"," userResponse":" fimbo"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947570133434","data":{"timestamp":" 947570133434"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_084616"," gameId":" 5d8c8bf6-4776-4fa0-8704-5008d452a3ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kutoa_fimbo-kutoa-asali"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kutoa"," userResponse":" kutoa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947570138735","data":{"timestamp":" 947570138734"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_084616"," gameId":" 5d8c8bf6-4776-4fa0-8704-5008d452a3ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_shina_macho-shina-apiyo"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" shina"," userResponse":" shina"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947570143814","data":{"timestamp":" 947570143814"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_084616"," gameId":" 5d8c8bf6-4776-4fa0-8704-5008d452a3ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_nyuki_jogoo-nyuki-mpaka"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" nyuki"," userResponse":" nyuki"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947570150248","data":{"timestamp":" 947570150248"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_084616"," gameId":" 5d8c8bf6-4776-4fa0-8704-5008d452a3ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_miguu_ofisi-mungu-miguu"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" miguu"," userResponse":" ofisi"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947570156639","data":{"timestamp":" 947570156639"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_084616"," gameId":" 5d8c8bf6-4776-4fa0-8704-5008d452a3ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_miguu_ofisi-mungu-miguu"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" miguu"," userResponse":" mungu"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947570162117","data":{"timestamp":" 947570162117"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_084616"," gameId":" 5d8c8bf6-4776-4fa0-8704-5008d452a3ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_miguu_ofisi-mungu-miguu"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" miguu"," userResponse":" miguu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947570167342","data":{"timestamp":" 947570167341"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_084616"," gameId":" 5d8c8bf6-4776-4fa0-8704-5008d452a3ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kindi_kindi-pekee-hajui"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kindi"," userResponse":" hajui"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947570173255","data":{"timestamp":" 947570173255"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_084616"," gameId":" 5d8c8bf6-4776-4fa0-8704-5008d452a3ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kindi_kindi-pekee-hajui"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kindi"," userResponse":" kindi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947570178410","data":{"timestamp":" 947570178410"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_084616"," gameId":" 5d8c8bf6-4776-4fa0-8704-5008d452a3ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_alama_ikiwa-alama-tamaa"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" alama"," userResponse":" ikiwa"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947570187735","data":{"timestamp":" 947570187735"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_084616"," gameId":" 5d8c8bf6-4776-4fa0-8704-5008d452a3ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_alama_ikiwa-alama-tamaa"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" alama"," userResponse":" tamaa"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947570193681","data":{"timestamp":" 947570193681"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_084616"," gameId":" 5d8c8bf6-4776-4fa0-8704-5008d452a3ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_alama_ikiwa-alama-tamaa"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" alama"," userResponse":" alama"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947570199058","data":{"timestamp":" 947570199058"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_084616"," gameId":" 5d8c8bf6-4776-4fa0-8704-5008d452a3ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_jamii_chake-jamii-erosi"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" jamii"," userResponse":" jamii"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947570204996","data":{"timestamp":" 947570204996"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_084616"," gameId":" 5d8c8bf6-4776-4fa0-8704-5008d452a3ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_tamaa_kizee-tamaa-vipya"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" tamaa"," userResponse":" tamaa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947570210416","data":{"timestamp":" 947570210416"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_084616"," gameId":" 5d8c8bf6-4776-4fa0-8704-5008d452a3ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kukaa_nyigu-kofia-kukaa"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kukaa"," userResponse":" kofia"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947570216261","data":{"timestamp":" 947570216261"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_084616"," gameId":" 5d8c8bf6-4776-4fa0-8704-5008d452a3ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kukaa_nyigu-kofia-kukaa"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kukaa"," userResponse":" kukaa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947570221180","data":{"timestamp":" 947570221180"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_084616"," gameId":" 5d8c8bf6-4776-4fa0-8704-5008d452a3ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_asije_asije-mengi-wingi"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" asije"," userResponse":" wingi"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947570227383","data":{"timestamp":" 947570227382"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_084616"," gameId":" 5d8c8bf6-4776-4fa0-8704-5008d452a3ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_asije_asije-mengi-wingi"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" asije"," userResponse":" asije"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947570233152","data":{"timestamp":" 947570233151"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_084616"," gameId":" 5d8c8bf6-4776-4fa0-8704-5008d452a3ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_asije_asije-mengi-wingi"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947570252235","data":{"timestamp":" 947570252235"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_084616"," gameId":" 1df41e3d-8b57-4992-903e-29b7a661b269"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_shina_macho-shina-apiyo"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" shina"," userResponse":" shina"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947570258467","data":{"timestamp":" 947570258467"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_084616"," gameId":" 1df41e3d-8b57-4992-903e-29b7a661b269"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_tamaa_kizee-tamaa-vipya"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" tamaa"," userResponse":" vipya"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947570264408","data":{"timestamp":" 947570264408"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_084616"," gameId":" 1df41e3d-8b57-4992-903e-29b7a661b269"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_tamaa_kizee-tamaa-vipya"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" tamaa"," userResponse":" tamaa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947570270327","data":{"timestamp":" 947570270327"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_084616"," gameId":" 1df41e3d-8b57-4992-903e-29b7a661b269"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kindi_kindi-pekee-hajui"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kindi"," userResponse":" hajui"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947570276175","data":{"timestamp":" 947570276175"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_084616"," gameId":" 1df41e3d-8b57-4992-903e-29b7a661b269"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kindi_kindi-pekee-hajui"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kindi"," userResponse":" pekee"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947570282160","data":{"timestamp":" 947570282160"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_084616"," gameId":" 1df41e3d-8b57-4992-903e-29b7a661b269"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kindi_kindi-pekee-hajui"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kindi"," userResponse":" kindi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947570287660","data":{"timestamp":" 947570287660"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_084616"," gameId":" 1df41e3d-8b57-4992-903e-29b7a661b269"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_alama_ikiwa-alama-tamaa"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" alama"," userResponse":" tamaa"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947570294080","data":{"timestamp":" 947570294080"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_084616"," gameId":" 1df41e3d-8b57-4992-903e-29b7a661b269"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_alama_ikiwa-alama-tamaa"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" alama"," userResponse":" ikiwa"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947570299887","data":{"timestamp":" 947570299887"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_084616"," gameId":" 1df41e3d-8b57-4992-903e-29b7a661b269"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_alama_ikiwa-alama-tamaa"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" alama"," userResponse":" alama"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947570306305","data":{"timestamp":" 947570306305"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_084616"," gameId":" 1df41e3d-8b57-4992-903e-29b7a661b269"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_miguu_ofisi-mungu-miguu"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" miguu"," userResponse":" ofisi"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947570312775","data":{"timestamp":" 947570312775"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_084616"," gameId":" 1df41e3d-8b57-4992-903e-29b7a661b269"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_miguu_ofisi-mungu-miguu"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" miguu"," userResponse":" miguu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947570321509","data":{"timestamp":" 947570321509"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_084616"," gameId":" 1df41e3d-8b57-4992-903e-29b7a661b269"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.5.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_miguu_ofisi-mungu-miguu"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"end":"end"}]}